Guide to the Joseph W. Martin papers, 1938-1952
Martin, Joseph W. papers, 1938-1952
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Joseph W. Martin papers, 1938-1952.
4377
Joseph W. (Joseph William) Martin, 1884-1968.
26 items.
Correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence with New York State political figures Frank E. Gannett, Daniel Alden Reed, Katharine St. George, and John Taber.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence with New York State political figures Frank E. Gannett, Daniel Alden Reed, Katharine St. George, and John Taber.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Martin, Joseph W. (Joseph William), 1884-1968.; Gannett, Frank E. (Frank Ernest), 1876-1957.; Reed, Daniel Alden, 1875-1959.; St. George, Katharine Price Collier.; Taber, John, 1880-1965.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Frank E. Gannett to JWM, Apr. 11, 1939 (Box 1)
  Sends books on industrial and labor relations in UK
- FEG to JWM, Apr. 14, 1939 (Box 1)
  Republican Party - political issues
- [JWM] to FEG, Apr. 20, 1939 (Box 1)
  Acknowledgement of Apr. 11, 1939 letter
- FEG to JWM, June 23, 1939 (Box 1)
  Telegram - against gov't spending
- FEG to JWM (and Republican National Committee), Sept. 18, 1942 (Box 1)
  Congressional elections; includes press release
- FEG to Republican Congressional Delegation, Oct. 9, 1942 (Box 1)
  Congressional elections
- FEG to JWM, Oct. 27, 1942 (Box 1)
- FEG to JWM, Nov. 19, 1942 (Box 1)
  FEG's resignation from Rep. Nat. Comm.
- JWM to FEG, Nov. 23, 1942 (Box 1)
- JWM to FEG, Nov. 24, 1942 (Box 1)
- JWM press release, Nov. 25, 1942 (Box 1)
- Daniel A. Reed to JWM, July 8, 1938 (Box 1)
- JWM to DAR, July 11, 1938 (Box 1)
- JWM press release, Feb. 28, 1939 (Box 1)
  Appointment of special Minority Committee on National Debt
- "Comm. on National Debt and Budget Policy", Feb. 28, 1939 (Box 1)
  Comm. roster; DAR at head of list
- DAR press release, July 26, 1939 (Box 1)
  Repr. of special committee on national defense
- JWM press release, Dec. 29, 1939 (Box 1)
  Copper tariff; Joseph W. Davies appointment
- Katherine St. George to JWM, Sept. 1, 1960 (Box 1)
  Thanks
- KSG to JWM, Sept. 20, 1962 (Box 1)
  Congratulations
- John Taber to JWM, Nov. 14, 1938 (Box 1)
  Congressional election
- JT to JWM, Aug. 8, 1939 (Box 1)
  Appropriations Comm.
- JT to JWM, Oct. 2, 1941 (Box 1)
  Lend Lease
- JT to JWM, Dec. 12, 1952 (Box 1)
- Secr. of JWM to JT, Dec. 15, 1952 (Box 1)
- JT to JWM, Dec. 16, 1952 (Box 1)
- JWM to JT, Dec. 22, 1952 (Box 1)